

Web Developer

mazejul@gmail.com

+44 (0)7519 265601 https://www.julien-maze.com https://github.com/djorak Moved to Scotland at the end if 2014 after 4 years of experience in web development in France. Highly motivated, hard-working and attentive to details. Always looking for a new challenge. Love new technologies and learning new things.

Experience

2014 - present

Web Developer

BBC Education - Glasgow, Scotland

- · Maintaining and adding new features to BBC Bitesize and iWonder using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP for the front-end
- · Creating a powerful Node.JS API to provide personalised curriculum data for the BBC Bitesize website and mobile application
- Creating a modern front-end for BBC Bitesize using Node.JS, React and Webpack
- · Maintaining and adding features to existing JAVA back-end services
- Using strong test driven development for all our projects
- Using AWS services (EC2, S3, Lambdas, API Gateway, Redis) to deploy and deliver our new services

2012 - 2014

Web Developer

Dickson-Constant – Lille, France

- Creating a mobile and desktop interactive UI from static designs
- · Maintaining and evolving the existing websites
- Improvements to a PHP REST API
- UI improvements to an Actionscript 3 awning simulator (Dickson designer)
- Setting up project management tools (SVN, Redmine)
- Setting up and managing dedicated servers (Debian)

2011 – 2012 **Web developer**

Abase – Brest, France

- · Creating an intranet for a newspaper company using Drupal
- Improvements on a bank budgeting application and CRM (Java, GWT)

2009 – 2010

Web developer ("sandwich course")

STDI – Lassay-les-Châteaux France

- Interactive school books for major French publishers.
- Educational apps and animations using Actionscript 2 & 3

Education

2007 - 2010

University Diploma of Technology (two-years) in Communication Services and Networks & Licence (one-year) in Multimedia and Web development

University Institute of Technology, Laval, France

Web development, project management, e-learning, graphic design, Front-End integration, photography, communication theory, networks administration

Skills

- HTML / CSS / SCSS
- Javascript (ES6) / jQuery
- Node.JS
- React, AngularJS
- Gulp, Grunt, NPM, Webpack
- PHP / MySQL
- Java

- OS: Windows, Linux, Mac OS
- · Tools: Atom, Git / SVN, Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator, JIRA, Confluence, Redmine, TDD with Mocha/Chai, BDD with Cucumber